https://newtreatments.org/privacy-policy/

Skip to contentHomePrivacy PolicyLast updated: July 9, 2019On this page, you can find our privacy policy regarding the information we obtain from you and how we use it in the provision of our service.You should be aware that your data won’t be shared with third parties except as documented in this Privacy Policy.The information gathered plays a tremendous role in not only the provision of our service but as well as improving it. By consenting to use the Service, you give us the mandate to gather and use these details as per the policy. The terms of use of this information are also described in our terms and conditions page at https://newtreatments.orgCollection of Information & UseWe would like to bring to your attention that when you opt to use our service, our company might ask you to provide personal data which in turn helps us acknowledge or reach out to you when need be.The personal details in question entail the following;NameEmail AddressLog Data Whenever you visit our Service, we obtain vital data that your browser sends to us. In most cases, the Log Data usually entails your IP Address, the page you most frequently visit, the version and type of browser you are using, when and where you visited our page from, how long you were on our site and other essential details.Cookies We advise our clients to accept cookies since they not only allow you to use our Service to the full extent. But, it also helps us gather relevant data which aids in the improvement of our service.You also have the freedom to not accept cookies, depending on your preference.Service Providers In order to conduct Service-related services, we do hire Third Party Companies, whom at times also provide the Service on our behalf.Your personal details can be accessed to some extent by these third parties when they are providing the service on our behalf. But, as they do this, they are under strict obligations not to share your information with anyone.Data Security As you may have observed in recent years, transmitting data over the internet has had its fair share of flaws. Its security cannot be guaranteed. However, we do take extreme precautions when it comes to protecting your data. We comply with data security regulations to keep your information safe.Links to Other Sites On our service, you will find links to other relevant sites. You should, however, know that we don’t operate these sites. They are operated by third parties. Before you begin using the service of Third Party Sites, it is advisable that you read their Privacy Policy first.Note that we are in no way responsible for any practises or policies carried out on third-party sites.The Privacy of Minors New Treatments does not collect or use data for minors; that is anyone below the age of 18.Our service does not intentionally collect or use the information provided by minors. In instances where a child provides us with personal information, we delete it from our servers. If a parent finds that their children have provided us with personal details, Contact Us immediately for assistance.Compliant with Legal Regulations Our service observes and adheres to all laws set regarding personal data.Privacy Policy Updates We advise users of our Service always to review our privacy policy frequently. This is because we are bound to change it time after time. Any changes will be posted on this page.Reach Out to Us In case you have any queries with our Privacy Policy, kindly reach out to us.Table of ContentsCollection of Information & UseLog Data Cookies Service Providers Data Security Links to Other Sites The Privacy of Minors Compliant with Legal Regulations Privacy Policy Updates Reach Out to Us Subscribe to Our Newsletter
Leave this field empty if you're human: Top PicksBest Kratom Vendors to Buy Kratom Online (2020)Coastline Kratom ReviewKratom Crazy Review 2020Kratom Near Me – Best Place to Find Kratom LocallyBest Places to Buy Kratom Online in 2020Popular Kratom StrainsMaeng Da KratomGreen Maeng Da KratomRed Maeng Da KratomWhite Maeng Da KratomBali KratomRed Bali KratomGold Bali KratomGreen Bali KratomWhite Bali KratomFresh From The BlogLeft Coast Kratom ReviewBest Verified Kratom Vendors to Buy Kratom Online (2020)Buy Kilogram Kratom With Bitcoin For Cheap Prices5 Best Places to Buy Kratom in Bulk Online With Credit CardsBest Kratom For Anxiety and Depression in 2020Best Kratom Strains To Mix For Different EffectsThe Best Kratom for EnergyBest Places to Buy Kratom Online in 2020The Most Euphoric Kratom Strain for Mood ElevationThe Best Kratom for Energy and Euphoria
